you
I
think you
know
well, you're
at work today. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We go here like I was
able to. But that you this is the tube strike. Right. But you you
are psycho.
Oh yeah, yeah, for you, it's fine. Okay. Cool. Yeah.
So yeah, waiting for thresh, I'm not sure whether he accepted my invite
now. It's not coming right? I don't know if that means he's not coming if he just doesn't
come to that. Let me check. Yeah. So
yeah. Yeah. Anyway, so if he's not coming, I don't know for some reason. Maybe I have done
some mistake. Yeah. So maybe we can discuss. Yeah. Cool. So what do you have been like? Yeah, we can have it.
I haven't actually made loads of progress. Sorry. So, you know, it came down to the wrong driver.
So I've got that resolved. And I've been looking at the problem is so in terms of libraries, I found
the, I found one which is in the like platform, I installed us as rent, please, and install. Then I
don't have any documentation in English. You're meeting for the Arduino or for the motor?
But so the library for the Arduino to talk to the motor. Yeah. So,
found once has no documentation in English, I can, is on platform iOS as easy to do. And then one
that does have documentation in English is not platform iOS. So it's been trying to work out one of those too.
I'm currently printing off. So I mean, the parts I should need to swap out the physical infrastructure.
So I've been structured for some of that about connecting cables. I think I might be able to
with 3D printed inserts. If not, we'll need to order in some like,
that's so first I might have some I can take. What do you need to order? Sorry.
I don't know. I might be able to get really 3D printing. So remember to let the stopper.
Okay. For the wire. Yeah. So I need something to make a loop with that. So in theory, I could do the same thing.
I just need to, I just need to see if I can actually get away with 3D printing a thing. And then,
okay, okay. Eating up the metal someone's ticket.
If you know some stopper, you can give it to me. I can order.
Yeah. Let me work it out.
By the end of the day, is it all right? Let's say, let me work out if I could do it with 3D printing.
If not, I'll send you the things to buy. I think we might also get some more bolts. So work out exactly
which bolts and inserts we need. And then send you that as well.
Yeah. Okay. So yeah. For the library for the motor, right? So can you ask pay you if he's there?
He can he might be able to help you because he this is his motor actually. But yeah, I think we
will get soon get the cube Mars motor. Yeah. It has been accepted actually now. And I've got all
the certificate so we can get the best motor. So yeah. So let's see, let's see fingers crossed
till now unless it gets solved. Yeah. I think I have basically worked out the library. It was just
a matter of translating the documentation. It wasn't in English. Is it all in? Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Is it it was in Chinese? I think so. Yes. I didn't actually check. I just used the book. But does the translation work?
Not completely. It translates to general meaning, but then it loses some specific technical language.
So you should be using. So this is the best translation I believe. It's deep L, right? Or something.
Yeah. I think deep L you should be using deep L are using this. This is the best translator for
technical one. You can try this and see it's here. Get it. I think it's I think we I think you can try.
Okay. Yeah. I have managed to work out most of the things because the function names stuff are still in English.
So yeah. If it's going on, which is set zero, I'm pretty sure I know about me. Okay. Okay. And it's kind of
thing of it doesn't. For example, like it translated point as indicator. Right. But I like I was able to work
it out. So can't you can't you just use my VS code scope highlight to directly do it?
You can use the co-pilot some some agent to do the translation and start the basic
codes for you. Uh, no. So the like the functions stuff is still written in English, but then the
external documentation in GitHub is written in Chinese. Yeah. So you can download the whole GitHub.
Yeah. So you can download my browser and using Google's template.
Maybe maybe you should. Okay. If it's working, it's fine, but maybe consider downloading the whole GitHub
and then make it as a VS code project and then use co-pilot to ask him to start an English
documentation for the whole project. It can read the projects because the files are in English,
right? And it can give you and its own documentation to start with.
Sure. Yeah. Okay. Oh, yes. I think I should be fine. I think I'll just end up taking a bit of time.
Okay. Oh, remember that. Oh, remember that.
The next time. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So I would say the easiest way is like, download any GitHub.
So do you have a Microsoft co-pilot? You can get a free co-pilot, you know, from education version.
You should register that. Do you know that? Yeah. I mean, I've like tried to do a couple of times.
I haven't really done what I wanted to. Yeah. You can ask him. You can ask. He has it. Actually,
you can ask how to do it. Chris, he did it already and he got the co-pilot approved as a student.
So now you have a good amount of what you call points to be used for a month and you can use them
for any kind of like. Yeah. It will be really helpful and fast. Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm looking forward to seeing the status and to communicate with the logic for
the service itself. I need to actually see the return character. Yes.
Okay. So yeah. So let's do it. And I don't know like the problem with me is that this figure
won't be we be able to come because the stupe strike every day and I need to take the picket
airline. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. So if you need any help, then we can just coordinate on remotely. I
think that's the easiest way. If you need to buy something, some small parts, you can make a list
as I told you before and send it to me. And yeah. So now the first idea is like
you're you're trying you need to do a initial testing, right? Whether the the delay between our
joint and the delay between the stepper and that sorry, this motor and that works or not,
right? That hypothesis. Okay. Yeah. Okay. So do you think like a week or two should be a good
timeline to like finish at least this part of the work or? Yeah. Yeah. For trying to think who I
still need to get done. I can't want to set the aim of by the end of the suite, but then. Okay.
Yeah. I'd like I think I should be able to get it done within a week. Okay. Okay. Now mine. Yeah.
So we got to is just okay. Just fine. Yeah. Yeah. So that we can at least get the idea to proceed,
you know, further. Yeah. Because even if we get the QMRS motor, those they did they are like now
two motors we'll be getting. So we'll be using that for the manipulator. We still need to fix the
issue with the other motors for the exhaust. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. So let's see. Yeah. So hopefully we'll
get it then. Yeah. Okay. Cool. Thank you. Anything else you want to discuss or share?
Uh, now we're good. Uh, yeah. If I've got any questions, I'll
then you will possibly ask me. Yes. Yeah. Just keep in touch. Yeah. Just that it's the week is
a sad week that there's so much strike is going on and so much to stuff. Yeah. Are they for
the strikes for the whole week or? Still Friday, midday, right? I think. Okay. Yeah. Like I don't
really follow two strikes. Yeah. You don't need to write you. You do take the yeah. I don't know how
Chris arrived of. Yeah. I mean, I took the district line yesterday. That was. Yeah. Monday was okay.
It started today, right? Okay. Yeah. Okay. I just got on the tube. Sorry. Okay. So,
but no, it's yeah, because I chewed up the family and Wimbledon Monday. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. What did you teach? Um, maths. Okay. Nice. Very good. Yeah. Yeah. Like the two-term maths is
pretty. Yeah. Like the high school middle school. I don't know how it works.
She sure I'm treating. She gives a GC level. Sorry. Oh. Okay.
Oh, I never do. Two meeting in the US. I think I was on the room call.
Oh, okay. So I think I made a mistake then. Oh, so I think every time I go to your
outlook and book a meeting. Yeah. And then, uh, okay, okay. So that creates duplicate meetings,
maybe it's my mistakes. I go to your link of for the outlook and book a slot. And then I come to
outlook and book a meeting. So I think no, no, no. Okay. That creates a meeting automatically.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I get it. I get it. I thought that you we use it to book a slot for you.
And then I need to create a meeting in that slot. It puts a team's link.
What do we know? Okay. Okay. Yeah. I think it was my fault. Yeah. I get it.
Oh, so I think I did it for your other meetings also.
Oh, yeah. Like for especially for the meeting with Dagmar and also.
You can do it. No, no, no, no, sorry. For the Dagmar one, I didn't book you yet.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. But that's when you can see a well of a slot from that and not
and then come to the other one. Yeah. From outlook directly. Right?
Oh, yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. So. Okay. So I was just discussing with Chris regarding what he did.
So yeah, I think. Yeah. So we are trying to now match. So maybe Chris can give you,
give tell you what he's now doing. Yeah. He's trying to do some hypothesis. Yeah.
Oh, sorry. Ben. Sorry. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So I thought you were going to go. So I'm currently modifying the robot arm.
So I've probably got a few bits printing upstairs and then we're working on. So I've got the
Adriano Uno and the DeBioMotor that they gave me. So I managed to find a library for it and
translate the documentation. So it's just I need to actually power up because there's the desktop
pass flow we've got takes plugs that might actually swap an outform with a screw game. So it's just
easier to connect up to the motor and the test motor and then I'll need to install the replacement
parts and swap up the cabling, which will be annoying. Should be fine. And then we can run a test
to see how much lack we get on the motor based on the rotary encoder. Yeah. That's one of the
we need to plug it out because the current plan is to use the step motor to adjust it.
And if you step much is too slow, then you'll be feeling like resistance when you try and move around.
So do we use a step motor or so? What is it better to use?
So Trisha, the idea is that we actually plan to use the step motor but then I think it's
I think we found a server motor from from pay you actually. He gave me a server motor. He brought
from China for a personal use. So we are trying to give it a shot. If it works, then maybe we can buy
some cheap server motors like like the decent one, not the cube marks one, the one we are planning
to order for them in a later. But maybe decent one, we can order if hypothesis works and we can
order something from robot shop very fast. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. I am a bit reluctant to use the
step motor because I don't think the step motor won't be able to match the, yeah. They're not
back drivable and they can miss steps if it was allowed. So that's why we have just got one
motor now, which we got from pay you and we are still trying to figure out the cube marks motor
from 3DXR. I think you have got all the email conversations cc to you, right? We got the compliance
certificate recently and now we can, I have also registered today 3DXR as our registered supplier,
ask the ICT to register them. And meanwhile, I have also asked HALA to create a VCC now so that
we can order because we have got the compliance certificate for the motors. And if we can get
the motors through VCC and if ICT accepts the 3DXR as our supplier, so next time we can I think
directly order. Cool. That's good. Yeah. We need back drivable motors. That's the planetary gear,
right? So the one you you were ordering, it has a planetary gear. Yeah. I don't know what is that
I think it had a planetary, so you have a central gear and then other like 304 rotating gears and
that makes it back drivable. I think these are all mostly gearless motor, right? It has a
gear, a planetary gear. Okay. Okay. But it's I think the ratio is one is to six or one is to eight.
Yeah, one is just six and back drivable. Yes. Very very good. These are like these are the motors
are used to design the human rights robots actually, actual motors. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They use it for
all the human rights robots. Yeah. That's good. So yeah, when will it come? No, we have I have asked HALA to
create a VCC for us. Then I can order and I think it should be able to if we can get the VCC
fast and then I think the order takes about a day or two. It's in stock. Yeah. VCC takes usually about
four to five days. Yeah. So once I order, then I think it should be pretty fast. Yeah. Okay. Cool.
Yeah. Yeah. So Ben is right. Good.
The the the wearable side
maybe if you have a do you have a can trolling with?
The can trolling loaded so I've been recovering
parts, uh, obviously. Um, it does the wearable side. It's a different setup to the one in the paper
you showed. Instead, we've got a single fixed pulley and then, uh, do separate
brunette packed cables with motors, the motors can tension the springs. We just at which
seem to be easier to make. Okay. Okay.
So the critical thing is allows us to adapt the tension in the spring independently so you can
change where the equilibrium points is too much. Right. So just can you see the purple two purple ones
like so they they don't dry the joint right? So it is it is just just stiffness. Yeah. So this is
kind of what we are doing with the main manipulator also. Right Ben? I think you're using the same
way. So what we will be doing is like this will be feeding the cables when the joint moves.
Yeah. Just it won't be pulling any getting any force. So it's like just a super nice the two.
That's what we and the purple ones. So we will try to synchronize with the we have a motor
encoder here, right? We will try to synchronize it with that. In the encoder feedback.
And then control that motor. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. We will that's what we are trying to test like
how what will be the latency between the two. Okay. Okay. That's the problem. Yeah.
There can be jitter coming from that like you know if there's any face like. Yeah. Right.
I am thinking of is there any mechanical way to couple them? So the the motor that drives the joints.
It's okay. So you mean like mechanical. But of course I think we are isolated from the joint.
Like so basically these tifters control is mounted on the on the shaft of this joint.
And then it always rotates with that. Yeah. So right now right now there the this pulley is actually
mounted on this joint. Yeah. And then and then let's say there is this motors are not powered.
So when you when we move this manipulator. So it will generate a bad driveable force to the motor.
Right. So that will add some extra stiffness to remove that. We will actively more move this
motors in the other direction so that they keep feeding the cables to the joints. So that we can
nullify that stiffness. That's the plan. Okay. Okay. Yeah. But then when when it comes to the
variable real variable thing. Yeah. We don't have motors. We can we can have motors with the back
right and then drive it through body and device when it is translated to him on head.
Okay.
But we can still have the encoder readings from the hand right. That is the actual hand joint and yeah.
And then translate that to the operators at the back.
Oh, I'm thinking just thinking like it looks like it is it is a it is a it's a big
intervention. So can we have a smaller motor which is almost bearable. Okay. And then have just
just give it the tag only like you know stiffness indicator only.
Good. Brother and giving the total stiffness required. Yeah. We are giving some delta theta only.
So it's like the movement. It's like the movement. Let's say it gets a disturbance right. We just
at that point there is a lag and we get the actual angle and then we can just apply some delta theta
in the opposite direction. So it just gives a tug that's the that's what actually I'm doing in simulation.
Yeah. So.
So right now this is the plan actually. So this is the actually joint following and we just give
the delta theta difference. That is coming from the bearable thing. That's a suit. Yeah.
Okay. So exosuit will give. So let's say the exosuit is following Q2 right. Q2 is the joint of
the elbow right. And let's say disturbance comes right. So we just give it like Q2 plus or Q2
minus delta theta and then it will just make those spring stiff in the other direction right.
That's your employee. So that stiffness we don't have to give the required total stiffness.
We can ask the joint to create the stiffness and then the stiffness signal you are giving from
the exosuit is just a error signal only. Let's say if your joint is already in the right stiffness
level it withdraws. It just stops giving you that delta theta or the stiffness command signal.
So just use the exosuit as a signal source. Okay. So otherwise like if we if we get the exosuit to
give that stiffness then the hand does nothing. Right. Okay. We are not getting the hand to work on that.
So when the hand is working properly so that I do does nothing. Does nothing right now it's
doing nothing because it's just feeding the cables in the other direction just to
feeding the cables in other direction. That's what it is doing. No, it's not fully fine. But the thing is
like we can then there's another step to minima kind of miniature eyes or make it lightweight so that
it is wearable on a human head. Okay. So the question is can we straight away jump to that?
The lightweight design where it generates basically is signal for the robot manipulator to act on that.
That means we need to remove this active coupling right.
Hmm. This coupling here. There can be a coupling but like not powerful motors. It is a simple.
You mean these two motors right purple? Yeah. Yeah. That is too much I think.
No, it's just for diagram actually. We are planning to use very simple motors, small motors.
Okay. Okay. Yeah. This is just what I have. It's just I made this is not the actual the cat diagram.
The cat drive ground. Okay. The actual cat diagram is the one used by Ben.
Right. But that's fine. Like I mean if we can have very light there are I think we already have them
in the lab like simple you couldn't bought a lot of them. Disc motors. Okay. Okay. So you're saying that
we've designed the exhaust suit in a lightweight manner and those small motors we just
but for the exhaust suit we need board and cables as well. So or maybe we can we can also or we can use
this cable. So we do the board and cables or we can route the pool cables.
Routing. I think routing is easier than boring. Yeah. Because it's like at the end it is just like
yarn routing. Yeah. But we make it as light as possible and then change the whole paradigm like
the exhaust suit is not not giving active talk. It is just giving a signal for the hand to work.
Okay.
So in the actual exhaust suit what I believe when we will get the small motors it's just gonna be
not doing it's gonna be actively working in the other direction right to just to keep the cables
a little bit taught right otherwise it will go slight. Then the hand feels that which way the
hand should be doing what the hand should be doing. Right. Yeah. It's like basically giving a
tug for you to move. Yeah.
Yeah with the mistake a lot of people are doing is they try to make the exhaust suit to work on
the movement rather than giving a signal. Yeah. Yeah. So we stay away from that.
Yeah.
Ben, Ben are you with us? Yes. Yeah. No. It matches what you were talking about.
When we talk about this last time a few weeks ago when you were training or it's more of the
assistive tool. Yeah. There's something other people are not trying. So other people try to overtake
the hand. We try to help the hand in a in a direct way. So giving it a signal. Okay.
This is what you should be doing. But sorry just to confirm you're still happy with the general
structure of the system. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just make it light. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So
yeah. So it's another word the prototyping stage. So we could use that. Of course.
It's very easy to use. Yeah. Like I'm writing that or I will ask you can I don't know where we put
those motors like those tiny step of motors. You can use them. Okay. Yeah. Okay.
Because the other thing I need to ask you is about getting access to the robotics. Oh yeah.
That's what you have a general general general access. Yes. Okay. Then I can submit a request.
Yes. The Parker can you give an induction to the robotics area? Okay. I think I've already taken him and given.
You have given. Okay. So then I'll I had to submit a request. I will do that now. Okay.
Yeah. I've probably been using the ideas lab upstairs because mainly because of the access to 3G printers.
But you're useful to ask to the robotics. Yeah. Of course. I'm just checking if Becky updated the list.
Should be because I've got car access to the general basement space. When I give him an
induction. When I give him do I need to register or do something or just give him a normal. No,
no. I have to register in there. Okay. Okay. I will do that now.
Okay. So I think
I think I have to ask whether he got the general induction yet or not as well.
I don't think he has unless he's done it. Okay. Yeah. Once he's done, let me know.
Still fat produce us. Okay. I had to edit the list.
Yeah. Cool. Cool. I think. Then how do you pronounce yours the last name? So S U.
R T double E. Yeah. S U R D double E. I need to put it in the chat.
S U R D E ES. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think. Yeah.
Yeah. Cool. I did that.
Did you didn't did you get a silicon workshop? Do you need? No. I don't need it.
If I need it in the future, I can ask. Yeah. Let me know. I get an induction.
If you need that. And then I submit.
Okay.
Okay. I submitted.
So it will go to the college and they will do it.
Yeah, so I think it is good.
And then I think till the motors come, then maybe Ben can have a look at what the motor specifications, the bunker is ordering.
So those motors will be for the manipulator which actually not for the exo.
Yeah, for the exo we could for him to know like so what is happening.
And I have sent him the link.
Yeah, look at the planetary gears and then the arrangements.
It's interesting. It's very, very cool.
Yeah, I've used the planetary gears before, it's not a planetary gearbox.
You have, okay.
Nice, nice.
Yeah, so I think that's the scope.
And then the challenge is to synchronize the manipulator motors and this exosuit motors.
We'll see how that goes.
Yeah, I mean, if there is a direct coupling mechanical coupling that much is better, like if we can think of it.
But we can start from somewhere.
Sorry.
We want a mechanical coupling because isn't the manipulator meant to implement with the arms so you wouldn't necessarily be able to connect.
Yes, actually.
I guess you basically like something that stays passive to the joint.
And then given a command, it's different.
That's all.
Yeah.
Yeah, so that's effective.
Yeah, so I guess the problem with my setup is it needs to actively with the current design is it needs to actively adapt to keep.
That's the thing that if you can avoid that problem.
And then if you can have a passive thing we can plug into that joint.
It just is so compliant and it moves with the manipulator and so lightweight that it is not going to add too much inertia to the thing.
But when we just give a signal, it can stiffen.
But I you know what one thing we can do is like we can we can have an on-off stiffness.
Yeah, because it's just a signal.
Okay.
Right, the bunker.
Yeah, I mean the problem is like we have analog stiffness that needs changing right.
But actually what we can do is like we can have this spring kind of constant.
And then have a PWM motor like it's like a more like a stiffness modulated with the PWM signal.
Right.
We can we can we can check if it works.
So basically we on and off a stiffness.
But with a PWM signal.
Okay.
What do you think Ben?
So you know a PWM is just just driving a motor with them.
0 5 0 5 but like on and off cycle due to cycle is basically you know playing with inertia right.
Yeah, and then rather than playing with inertia how about like you know couple it with stiffness.
Diffness of the spring or stiffness of the joints stiffness of the spring was spring.
Yeah.
So this is just one spring.
We can have just one spring and then it is just adding a stiffness to the joint that all.
Yeah, because we all what you need is a stiffness signal.
It is not really a stiffness right.
So is this stiffness that stops the on from moving.
In that case why.
Just look at other options could you use a system other than a spring and a motor like I'm thinking what if you had like a break pad type thing.
So yeah, that is a damper right not just stiffness.
So so it is giving a damper like we can have a clutch that still you know switches right.
It is giving a damping effect but if you can have a spring loaded clutch for example.
Yeah, right that might be interesting.
So we can explore those those things because all what we need is a signal.
Is it a signal from where sorry from the off as a stiffness or impedance signal to the to the manipulator basically the robot manipulator suddenly feels that something is impeding it.
Oh, so it's so you use the motor is a force sensor rather than.
Yeah, it's not actually it is just giving a signal to the manipulator saying okay you should generate some stiffness and then I'm indicating you what you should be doing.
Okay, and how would the suit generate the stiffness.
The when you have the backgrabble borders we can change its its its begin or begin.
Like we can create that stiffness.
Actually we can have that stiffness change a mechanism in the in the way you have shown.
Okay, so this is the actual stiffness control mechanism.
Yeah, that is part of the manipulator right.
We need additional variable like a very lightweight variable thing that gives the signal.
How which will be changing the stiffness.
So sorry, so right now the exhaust would be our the motors and those those two cables are replicating the exhaust right.
Yeah, what I'm saying is rather than doing that we use these motors to do actual stiffness control like you know you have powerful motors there.
Yeah.
So you don't need the springs.
You can just have the like you.
You need the springs to give stiffness.
I mean if we cannot if cannot do that with.
I mean you are simulating co-contration of muscles right.
But then we have additional exhaust which is just giving the signal.
It is giving us stiffness signal till the the manipulator stiffness reaches the desired level.
Yeah, okay.
Right and then the exhaust would stop giving that signal.
When the manipulator reaches the right stiffness.
It's like a horse rider so you are you keep giving waves to the horse till it picks up the speed and then you stop.
What determines the correct stiffness.
Oh, that comes from that contraction theory algorithm.
I'm not.
Yeah, I can explain.
Yeah, I'm not really aware of.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, it's fine.
So I think it's a control algorithm that just generates a correct level of stiffness and damping.
And then now the robot has to.
Manipulate that and then but like we decouple that we are saying.
The brain cannot really.
The brain doesn't know how to generate that brain doesn't have that algorithm.
Let's say, okay.
So and the brain, even if it has it, it cannot generate that stiffness.
Now what we do is we have a artificial exhaust suit that has that algorithm of generating the contraction level.
And then it it teaches the brain how to get to that.
Right. So that also by giving a signal.
Okay, can you can you stiffer little bit more and things like that.
And then it is just a guide.
And the brain is trying to learn in the background.
So if the robot manipulator is let's say ideal brain.
It learns what the exhaust knows at some point.
That is what we are simulating.
Is that is that right?
Yes.
I'm just thinking like we will also consider the manipulator as our impaired arm, right?
Impair down with the.
Yeah, with the stiffness control mechanism as the brain that part of the brain that should be.
Yeah.
A stiffness control.
Let's say it is impaired and then it doesn't know.
Basically, it is getting a signal from outside to learn that impairment.
Oh, composite for that impaired.
Because the robot manipulator is ideal.
It will learn it as far as the signal comes.
Yeah.
What we are saying is we assume that the brain first doesn't know how to recover.
And then with the with the exhaust food that knows how to do the math.
We'll give the signals to it.
It's like, but we are starting the manipulator with a very weak spring here, right?
So it is already.
Yeah, that's like it has a baseline something.
Yeah, so it's very weak, right?
So if we there is always a lag between when we pull the cable here and then it reaches the position.
It's very weak, right?
And I'm sure that if it strikes something because the stiffness is so weak that it's going to be oscillating a lot, right?
If the damping is also.
Yeah, so at some point it should it should first start with that very weak thing.
And then it should it should come to the right level of stiffness.
Yeah, so when we add these two springs, so it is actually multiplying.
It is adding the effective stiffness.
Now it's going to be something like K effective R square, right?
Yeah, so there's real stiffness is coming from the two more test co-contracting.
Yeah, these two, right?
Yeah.
So those two pulling together will create the co-contraction.
Yeah, so this is the what it is.
So let's say when without it, it's going to move very.
It's going to move and not properly if it strikes something that's a disturbance.
And then at that time these motors will be activated.
And then it will just try to bring it back to the nominal position, right?
Yeah, yeah, at that.
So this is I think what we are doing, but I still didn't understand you said we need some like
instead of this kind of coupling, we need some active coupling, you know,
to make it from the episode because I was also thinking like.
No, there's also this separate thing now.
So this is this is the stiffness control mechanism.
Yeah.
And that is not the episode.
So that is basically.
Okay, so now we are simulating two parts of the brain, right?
So one part of the brain is motion control.
Yeah, it is just doing motion control, joint motion.
And then another part of the brain doing stiffness control.
Yeah.
And then there are two controllers independent controllers, one supporting the other, right?
So basically stiffness control is supporting the movement
to generate some stable force interaction.
Yeah.
Now say your stiffness control mechanism is now impaired.
Now it has to learn the best stiffness level given the disturbance.
It doesn't know how to do that.
Either it is weak or doesn't know.
And then now then we have a signal coming from the exhaustor which is the third layer.
Yeah.
Right.
And saying, okay, so like this is a reward or punish for something like a reward or a teaching signal.
Okay, given this disturbance, I will give you a stiffness signal so that you can try to learn that.
So it is sitting on top of all these things and then adding a stiffness to the joint.
We never needed it.
And then the purple motors should try to you know, follow that and kind of identify that.
Right.
So next time when there's a disturbance, if the purple motors does fairly a good job,
then the exhaustor doesn't do much.
So it just says, okay, passively stays there.
But is there something missing?
Then it'll activate that stiffness and give that signal.
Yeah.
So the exhaustor will be, so it's this is our hand, right?
So the exhaustor will be the main controller which will be controlling these two motors, right?
The exhaustor will be a third one, third addition.
So why do we then why do we have these springs for the manipulator?
We don't need them, right?
Then we can just have the as far as the motors are back drivable, then then you don't need them.
Yeah, for the if they are a step a motor, then you need them.
Yeah, it's a back drivable motor.
So so we don't need the manipulator springs, then, right?
You don't need them.
Yeah, we just need the springs for the this this other other two motors.
Exactly.
Yeah.
If you need the baseline stiffness, you can have it, but like it's duplicating efforts.
So what's the next steps?
I think let's get let's get these two work first.
And then we add the exhaustor later.
Yeah, I will.
Yeah, for the real arm, okay, we have the arm and then we put the exhaustor and this mechanism of the two motors will be on top of the.
Right?
Yeah, so the exhaustor will be a third addition to this.
No, I mean like the actual picture we're looking at.
Yeah, not from the this reward, you know, like like a human when he is wearing it.
Yeah, so the manipulator will be the arm.
So then he will wear the some some some kind of I don't know, he's going to wear some kind of textiles stuff, right?
Right.
And then on top of that, we will have these two cables and motors, right?
So we are just separating the stiffness control and motion control on purpose here.
Yeah.
And then we learn the two kind of complimentary mechanisms in parallel.
Sorry.
I think we can we can go backwards and then we can get your.
Contraction theory implemented in this manipulator without any exhaustor first and then see if it really works, right?
Yeah.
And then we pretend that we don't have that and then we get to the exhaustor.
Yeah, so we'll first use the contraction based controller to find out that stiffness, right?
Yeah.
That's actually the plan.
And then can focus on that.
This this this stiffness control.
Part first and then when we'll understand what the contraction control is doing and then once we are comfortable with that, then we can think of.
The exosuit part, which is which is a complication like so it is a add on.
I think we can keep thinking about it, but like we don't have to come up with the solution right now.
We have enough problem to solve in this this setup.
Yes.
I believe first problem is the the delay between those.
Yeah, the latency.
Yeah.
And check it was still productive for me to modify it and then get the step and motor.
I will continue to work on that.
There.
Shouldn't take more than a week.
And then we can look at the next.
Yeah.
Cool.
Yeah, let's let's do this and we'll learn lessons from this and then we can think of improvements later.
Let's get a basic thing to work first.
Yeah.
Cool.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
I brought your coffee.
I'll bring it to the office now.
Oh, thank you.
So you are how did you reach work today with the strike?
Yeah, there were strikes and then luckily I escaped it.
And then it's trying to start from 12 to 12.
So the way home I will I will have trouble.
Okay.
But the train is okay, right?
It's just the tube, right?
It's just a tube.
Yeah.
Maybe I had to find a way to get to what loop us 10 then.
I'll get the train.
Yeah, I will cycle.
I don't know.
All right.
Enjoy.
Oh, yeah, see.
He will work.
Yeah, but he's cycle to work every day.
Yeah, yeah, it's not the best.
The end of bicycle.
But I don't know.
I'm.
Must act my atmosphere.
I want you to borrow.
Okay, cool.
Otherwise, that walk.
Walk to what a loop.
Oh, I got how long you throw.
It's far right?
The I think I mean, there's buses as well.
Yeah, there are better buses.
I think we're 14 and then.
That's another one.
I can't remember.
Yeah, I'll.
Cool.
So I'll be in the coffee.
Okay.
See you.
Thank you.